# **Asaf Marom**

# Full-stack developer

A passionate and driven full-stack web developer with knowledge and experience in the latest web technologies. A self-motivated individual that can thrive in a team environment as well as individually, with a diverse background in sales and operations.

### Work Experience



Full-Stack Web Developer Freelance 2022 - present

- Building websites and landing pages in, Javascript, React, PHP, WordPress for clients across different industries.
- Built several demand-driven apps and games, including a Hebrew version of Wordle and a random restaurant generator for Wolt and 10Bis.



Full-Stack Web Developer <u>Dice Marketing</u> 2021-2022

- Oversaw the development of a wide range of of projects from simple landing pages to complex web applications (dashboard for "Adam-milo", CMS system for cruises).
- Used PHP, WordPress, Javascript, React , Nextjs and Redux.
- Worked hand in hand on projects with other programmers collaborating with GitHub, UX/UI designers, Monday.com.



Operations Manager <u>Vered Tours</u> 2018-2020

- Built and implemented comprehensive social media strategy and website.
- Oversaw and organized travel logistical operations for large groups with varied needs.
- Also functioned as a sales representative for prospective customers



Sales Account Manager & Customer Success  $\underline{Rentigo}$ 

2017 -2018

- Responsible for B2B & B2C sales and meeting company sales targets, developing customer relationships that promote retention and loyalty.
- Working closely with marketing and R&D to improve company progress and success.
- Respond promptly to customer inquiries, building trust & loyal partnerships.

#### Education

2020 | Full Stack Web Developer, Elevation Academy

 An industry-based intensive 3-month coding bootcamp which covered the entire MERN stack.

2016 -2019 | B.A. Marketing, Sapir College

 Courses include: Market research, marketing communications and strategy, company analysis with advanced methods and models and more.

## Contact Info

Click here to view my portfolio

Phone: +972-54 544 9151

<u>LinkedIn</u>

<u>Email</u>

Tel Aviv, Israel

# Relevant Skills

- Programing in modern JavaScript (ES6) to build a full-scale web application
- Building MVC, frameworks, Single page apps, Progressive Web Applications (PWA) with React; Flux state management (Redux, MobX)
- Client side developing expertise with: Javascript, TypeScript, React, next.js, Vue.js, CSS, HTML, JQuery, Materialize, tailwind)
- Orchestrating backend application using Node.js, Express, MongoDB, Mongoose, SOL
- Emphasis on modern developing tools (ci/cd), using: Git, Github, bitbucket, Heroku, Vercel

### **Hobbies & Interests**

I enjoy playing frisbee, especially freestyle!

